

Kyiv, Ukrainein abratanin

SKILLS

.Net C# ASP.NET Core

Docker Microservices

Domain Driven Design EF Core

MSSQL Postgres

Windows Services Linux Services

Quartz CI/CD

Git Unit Testing

Integration Testing Bash

Powershell OOP

Scrum

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian Russian
Native Speaker Proficient

English Upper-

Intermediate

Andrii Bratanin

Self-managed developer who likes to investigate and whose work experience focuses mostly on back-end. I would like to complement a strong proactive "continuous delivery"-aware development team working on a project that requires to make long-term architectural decisions and master new technologies, thus encouraging to gain new expertise and grow skills. I am fond of automation, containerization and virtualization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Luxoft (08/2012 - 11/2013)

.Net Developer

• Financial Analytic System to detect violations in auctions.

GlobalLogic (11/2013 - 11/2014)

.Net Developer

• Backup and Recovery solution for home and business needs.

Infopulse (11/2014 - 11/2015)

.Net Developer

• Big Four-size Human Resources Management System

Ciklum (12/2015 - 11/2018)

Senior .Net Developer

Solution to automate printing services with strict SLAs for a worldwide known Client.

- Retail management system for famous wine distributor.
- Solution to facilitate and automate Visa checks and issues.

NDA (11/2018 - 06/2019)

Senior .Net Developer

• Crypto Fintech Startup

Svitla Systems (07/2019 - Present)

Senior .Net Developer

Hospitality, Hyatt-size Hotel Management System

DOMAINS

Crypto, E-commerce, Electronic document circulation, Fintech, HR & Recruiting, Statistics, Data communication

EDUCATION

Bohdan Khmelnytsky National University of Cherkasy (08/2003 - Master's Degree (with honours), Software of Automatic Computer 06/2009)

Systems

National Academy of Science, Kiev Institute of Mathematical (08/2009 - Machines & System 08/2012)

Postgraduate, Information Secutiry in Open Public Networks